Guide to the Ralph W. Tyler Papers 1932-1988
University of Chicago Library
- Series I: University of Chicago - Dean, Department, & Division
  - W. W. Kellogg Foundation, Michigan Community Health Area, Eaton County Workshop, 1942 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - W. W. Kellogg Foundation, Michigan Community Health Area, Allegan County Workshop, 1942 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Kennedy-Kirkendall (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Klaus-Kuehn (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Laboratory Schools, University of Chicago (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Laboratory Schools, University of Chicago (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - LaMalfa-Lazenby (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Leagons-Leyden (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Liddle-Little (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Lloyd-Lyon (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Maaske-McClure (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - McConnell-McGuire (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Machine Shop, Department of Education (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - McKeon-May (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Meacham-Memmott (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Memoranda, Department of Education (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Merson-Millikan (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Mirrielees-Mitchell (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Monroe-Mitchell (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Makosteen (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - National Association for Research in Science Teaching (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - National Association-National Research Council (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - National Society for the Study of Education 1945 Yearbook, correspondence A-G (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - National Society for the Study of Education 1945 Yearbook, correspondence R-Z (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - National Society for the Study of Education 1945 Yearbook, minutes (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - National Society for the Study of Education 1945 Yearbook, American Education in the Postwar Period, "Introduction" by R. W. Tyler; Chapter I by Ruth Andrus (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - National Society for the Study of Education 1945 Yearbook, American Education in the Postwar Period, Chapter II by H. T. Morse (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - National Society for the Study of Education 1945 Yearbook, American Education in the Postwar Period, Chapter III by Maurice F. Seay (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - National Society for the Study of Education 1945 Yearbook, American Education in the Postwar Period, Chapter IV by Muriel Brown (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - National Society for the Study of Education 1945 Yearbook, American Education in the Postwar Period, Chapter V by Milda Taba (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - National Society for the Study of Education 1945 Yearbook, American Education in the Postwar Period, Chapter VII by C. L. Cushman John B. Mason (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - National Society for the Study of Education 1945 Yearbook, American Education in the Postwar Period, Chapter VIII by H. H. Wilson (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - National Society for the Study of Education 1945 Yearbook, American Education in the Postwar Period, Chapter IX by William Seyfert (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - National Society for the Study of Education 1945 Yearbook, American Education in the Postwar Period, Chapter X by Ruth Strang (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - National Society for the Study of Education 1945 Yearbook, American Education in the Postwar Period, Chapter XI by H. Harap and J.E. Mendenhall (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - National Society for the Study of Education 1945 Yearbook, American Education in the Postwar Period, Chapter XII by G. R. Gant (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - National Society for the Study of Education, 1949 Yearbook (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - National Society of College Teachers-News Letter (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - News Letter, Department of Education (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Nichols-Noel (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - North Central Association of Colleges and Universities (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Northwestern-Novak (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Nursery School, University of Chicago (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - "O" Correspondence (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Palmer-Philadelphia (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Pickett-Prall (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Preparation of Teachers, University Committee on; 1940-6 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Preparation of Teachers, University Committee on; 1947-8 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Preparation of Teachers, University Committee on (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Preparation of Teachers, University Committee on; 1948 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Preparation of Social Science Teachers, University Subcommittee on (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Prescott, Daniel (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Press, University of Chicago (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Progressive Education Association (American Education Fellowship), Eight Year study, 1946 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Prosser Resolution (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Protheroe-Pruitt (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - "Q" correspondence (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Radio, Board of (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Randall (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Random-Ray (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Reading Clinic, Department of Education (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Redfield-Registrar (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Registration figures, Department of Education (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Rehmus-Robinson (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Robinson Foundation (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Rochester Institute of Technology (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Rockefeller Foundation (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Rockwell-Rondileau (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Rosenwald Foundation (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Ross-Rugg (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Rural Editorial Service (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Rural Editorial Service (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Rural Editorial Service (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Rural Editorial Service (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Rural Editorial Service (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Rural Editorial Service (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Rural Education-Ryans (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Saenger-Scroggs (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Seachore-Seeman (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Senate, Committee of the Council of, University of Chicago (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Seyfert-Shankland (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Shankman Foundation (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Shaw-Shyder (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Social Education (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Social Sciences Division, meetings (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Social Sciences Division, Executive Committee; 1938-1941 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Social Sciences Division, Executive Committee; 1942 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Social Sciences Division, Executive Committee; 1943 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Social Sciences Division, research plans (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Social Science Research Committee, 1944 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Social Science Research Committee, 1945 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Social Science Research Committee, 1946 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Social Science Research Committee, Project Requests for 1946-7 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Social Science Research Council (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Social Science Research Council (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Social Science Research Council (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Social Science Research Council (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Society-Spaulding (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Specialized Child Care, Committee on, University of Chicago (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Speer-Spitznas (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Stafford-Stone (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Storm-Studebaker (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Student Activities Committee, Department of Education (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Study-Superintendents (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Surveys of Schools, general (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Surveys of Schools, Dalton School Survey, Report (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Surveys of Schools, Dalton School Survey, 1942 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Surveys of Schools, Dalton School Survey, January-February 1943 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Surveys of Schools, Dalton School Survey, March-May 1943 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Surveys of Schools, Dalton School Survey, September 1944-March 1946 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Surveys of Schools, Dalton School Survey, April 1946-August 1947 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Surveys of Schools, Dalton School Survey, Committee Reports (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Surveys of Schools, Dalton School Survey, miscellaneous (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Surveys of Schools, Dalton School Survey, Society- Spaulding (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Surveys of Schools, Dalton School Survey, New York City Schools Survey of Curriculum experiment, 1940 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Surveys of Schools, Dalton School Survey, 1941 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Surveys of Schools, Dalton School Survey, 1941 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Surveys of Schools, Dalton School Survey, 1941 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Surveys of Schools, Dalton School Survey, folder I, II, III (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Surveys of Schools, Dalton School Survey, Sample tests (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Surveys of Schools, Dalton School Survey, Bibliography and reprints (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Surveys of Schools, Dalton School Survey, Reports (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Surveys of Schools, Dalton School Survey, Reports (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Surveys of Schools, Dalton School Survey, Miscellaneous (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Surveys of Schools, Dalton School Survey, Wells High School (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Surveys of Schools, Dalton School Survey, Wells High School (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Surveys of Schools, Dalton School Survey, Willmette Schools, Observer’s reports (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Surveys of Schools, Dalton School Survey, questionnaires (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Surveys of Schools, Willmette Schools, reports (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Surveys of Schools, Willmette Schools, miscellaneous (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Surveys of Schools, Winnipeg Schools (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Surveys of Schools, Winnipeg Schools (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Surveys of Schools, Winnipeg Schools (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Surveys of Schools, Winnipeg Schools (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Sutton-Szilard (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Taba-Texas (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Thelen, Herbert (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Thelen, Herbert (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Thompson-Travers (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Triggs-Tyler (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - R. W. Tyler, press releases (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Unesco (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - United States Department of Agriculture Extension Service, Studies Program of the Division of Field Studies and Training, general (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - United States Department of Agriculture Extension Service, Studies Program of the Division of Field Studies and Training, Northeastern Regional workshop (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - United States Department of Agriculture Extension Service, Studies Program of the Division of Field Studies and Training, Workshop on extension Administration, Wisconsin University (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - United States Department of Agriculture Extension Service, Studies Program of the Division of Field Studies and Training, Workshop on Extension Supervision, Ohio State University (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - United States Department of Agriculture Extension Service, Studies Program of the Division of Field Studies and Training, Workshop on Extension Supervision, Alabama (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - United States Department of Agriculture Extension Service, Studies Program of the Division of Field Studies and Training, Supervisory Workshop, Pullman, Washington (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - United States Department of Agriculture Extension Service, Studies Program of the Division of Field Studies and Training, Workshop on Supervision, North Carolina (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - United States Department of Agriculture Extension Service, Studies Program of the Division of Field Studies and Training, Extension Evaluation Workshop, Chicago (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - United States Department of Agriculture Extension Service, Studies Program of the Division of Field Studies and Training, Extension Evaluation Workshop, Chicago (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - United States Department of Agriculture Extension Service, Studies Program of the Division of Field Studies and Training, Extension appraisal, New Jersey (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - United States Department of Agriculture Extension Service, Studies Program of the Division of Field Studies and Training, Department of Agriculture Graduate School Course 700, Washington (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - United States Department of Agriculture Extension Service, Studies Program of the Division of Field Studies and Training, Colorado Burner School graduate course in extension evaluation (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - United States Department of Agriculture Extension Service, Studies Program of the Division of Field Studies and Training, Workshop for State Home Demonstration Leaders, Lafayette, Indiana (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - United States Federal Security Agency (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - University College, University of Chicago (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Van Cleave-Verde (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Vocational Guidance and Placement, Board of, University of Chicago (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Vocational Guidance and Placement, Board of, University of Chicago (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Vocational Guidance and Placement, Board of, University of Chicago (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Vocational Guidance and Placement Bulletins, University of Chicago (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Volberding-Vossbrink (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Wade-Way (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Weber-Whitford (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Wickham-Wittick (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Woellner-Woody (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Workshops, Department of Education (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Workshops, Department of Education (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Workshops, Department of Education (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Workshops, Department of Education (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - World-Wyoming (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Y, Z (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Unidentified manuscript about German School books (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Unidentified manuscript about German School books (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Unidentified manuscript about German School books (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Unidentified manuscript about German School books (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Unidentified manuscript about German School books (Box 25, Folder 8)
- Series II: Biographical and Personal
  - Biographical material, resumes (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Biographical material, awards and honors (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Biographical material, honorary degrees (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Biographical material, copies of publications (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Biographical material, photographs (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Dissertations about Tyler, list (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Dissertation by Richard D. Levy, Temple University, "A Study of Ralph W. Tyler’s Statement, Development, and Later Modifications of His Rationale as Set Forth in Basic Principles of Curriculum and Instruction." (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Dissertation by Martha Elin Vernazza, University of California, Berkeley, "The Evaluation Principles of Ralph W. Tyler: Criteria for Decision-Makers and Program Evaluators," pgs. 1-173. (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Dissertation by Martha Elin Vernazza, University of California, Berkeley, "The Evaluation Principles of Ralph W. Tyler: Criteria for Decision-Makers and Program Evaluators," pgs. 174-269. (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Martha Elin Vernazza, curriculum vitae and manuscript, "A Review of the Literature of Ralph Tyler as It Pertains to the Evaluation of Educational Programs," 1980. (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Manuscript by Joe O'Shea, "A Journey to the Midway; Ralph Winfred Tyler," 1985. (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Material on outcome-based education (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - RWT course syllabus, Education T-50, Curriculum Theory (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, 1966-1991, including letter from Bruno Bettelheim to Tyler, October 20, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Note and manuscript by Ralph Tyler, Jr., "A Teacher in the Family," 1988. (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - RWT's vita and list of professional honors, news clippings, and other miscellany related to his professional career (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Copy of program papers for "Ralph W. Tyler in Retrospect; Contributions to the Curriculum Field," 1981 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Transcript of Phi Delta Kappa interview with RWT, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Information on the Ralph Tyler Oral History Project, University of California, Berkeley, 1986 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Itineraries, July-December 1970 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Itineraries, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Itineraries, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Itineraries, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Itineraries, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Itineraries, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Itineraries, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Itineraries, 1977 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Itineraries, 1978 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Itineraries, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Itineraries, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Itineraries, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Itineraries, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Itineraries, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Itineraries, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Itineraries, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Itineraries, 1986 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Itineraries, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Ralph W. Tyler Project, Lyndon B. Johnson Library (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Ralph W. Tyler Project, National Foundation for the Improvement of Education (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Ralph W. Tyler Project, handwritten notes (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Ralph W. Tyler, clippings and press releases (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Ralph W. Tyler Oral History Project (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Ralph W. Tyler Oral History Project, fundraising (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - NEC Salute to Dr. Ralph W. Tyler (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Oral History transcript (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence regarding manuscript between Lackey and Tyler; Manuscript by George H. Lackey, Jr. and Michael D. Rowls, "Wisdom in Education; The Views of Ralph Tyler," Preface and Part I. (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Manuscript by George H. Lackey, Jr. and Michael D. Rowls, "Wisdom in Education; The Views of Ralph Tyler," Part II. (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Manuscript by George H. Lackey, Jr. and Michael D. Rowls, "Wisdom in Education; The Views of Ralph Tyler," Part III. (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Manuscript by George H. Lackey, Jr. and Michael D. Rowls, "Wisdom in Education; The Views of Ralph Tyler," Part IV. (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence between RWT and Dr. Thomas Hale Ham, M.D., of Dartmouth Medical School, 1974-1978 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Draft of "An Open Letter on Inquiry in Medical Education," by Dr. Thomas Hale Ham, M.D. (Box 28, Folder 14)
- Series III: Correspondence
  - Subseries 1: Correspondence, 1942-1945
    - A (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - American Association of School Administrators (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - B (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Ca (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Cl-Col (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Cooperative Study in General Education, 1941-2 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Cooperative Study in General Education, 1943 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Corey, Stephen M., 1942 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Corey, Stephen M., 1943 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Corey, Stephen M., 1943 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Corey, Stephen M., 1944 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Con-Cu (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - D (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - E (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Edmonson, J. B. (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - F (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Faculty Assignments (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Filbey, Emory T. (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - G (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - General Education for Men in the Armed Services [Committee on a Design for General Education for Members of the Armed Forces, 1943] (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - General Education for Men in the Armed Services [Committee on a Design for General Education for Members of the Armed Forces, 1943] (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - General Education for Men in the Armed Services [Committee on a Design for General Education for Members of the Armed Forces, 1943] (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - General Education for Men in the Armed Services [Committee on a Design for General Education for Members of the Armed Forces, 1943] (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - H (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Hull House Assistantship (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Hutchins, Robert Maynard (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Huth, C. F. (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - I-K (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - W. W. Kellogg Foundation Budgets, 1941-3 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - L (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Lyons Township High School (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - M (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Miller, Fred A. (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - National Defense (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - National Education Association (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - National Safety Council (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - O (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Orthopedic School [Committee on the Study of] (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - P (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Progressive Education Association [P.E.A.] Nominating Committee (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - R (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Radio (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Reavis, William C. (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Redfield, Robert (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - S (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Social Science Research Committee (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Social Science Research Committee (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Social Science Research Committee, 1939-1941 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Social Science Research Committee, 1942 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Social Science Research Committee, 1943 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - State Testing Program (Illinois) (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - T (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Teacher Education [Commission on], 1941 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Teacher Education [Commission on], 1942 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Teacher Education [Commission on], 1943-4 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Teacher Education [Commission on], Draft of Commission Report (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Teacher Education [Commission on], Evaluation for Student Personnel (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Teacher Education [Commission on], Evaluation for Colorado State (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - University War Activities (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - V-Z (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Subseries 2: Correspondence, 1946-1982
    - Ac-Am (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - An-Au (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Abington Conference (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Academy of Independent Scholars (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - African Regional Seminar for Advanced Training in Systematic Curriculum Development and Evaluation (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - American Academy of Arts and Sciences (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - American Association for the Advancement of Science (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - American Association of School Administrators (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - American Association of School Librarians (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - American College Testing Program (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - American Council on Education (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - American Educational Research Association, 1974-1975 (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - American Educational Research Association, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - American Educational Research Association, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 20)
    - American Educational Research Association, 1978-9 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - American Educational Research Association, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - American Educational Research Association, 1981 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - American Educational Research Association, 1982-5 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - American Educational Studies Association (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - American Institutes for Research (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - American Orthopsychiatric Association (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - American Psychiatric Association (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - American Psychoanalytic Association (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - American Society for Engineering Education (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - American Society for Training and Development (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - American Vocational Association (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Antioch College (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Archdiocese of Chicago School Office (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Association for Individually Guided Education (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Association for Supervision and Curriculum Development (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - Association of American Medical Colleges (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - Association of California School Administrators (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - Athenian School (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - Aurora College (Box 34, Folder 20)
    - Ba-Bu (Box 34, Folder 21)
    - Boston College (Box 34, Folder 22)
    - Brookings Institution (Box 34, Folder 23)
    - Burlington Community College (Box 34, Folder 24)
    - C (Box 34, Folder 25)
    - California, Advisory Committee on Achievement and Evaluation (Box 34, Folder 26)
    - California, Department of Education (Box 34, Folder 27)
    - California, Governor's Advisory Committee on Children and Youth (Box 34, Folder 28)